<resources>

    <!--MAIN-->
    <string name="app_name">Seahawk Tours</string>
    <string name="mainTitle">Seahawk Tours</string>
    <string name="UNCW_Building_Archives_URL">https://library.uncw.edu/web/collections/archives/landmarks.html</string>


    <!--ABOUT ACTIVITY-->
    <string name="aboutNames">Created by: \nRiley Caldwell \nDavid Brunk \nMatthew Harris</string>
    <string name="aboutString1">UNCW building information and images courtesy of the</string>
    <string name="aboutString2"><a href="https://library.uncw.edu/web/collections/archives/landmarks.html">UNCW University Archives</a></string>

    <!--CIS BUILDING-->
    <string name="CISBuildingName">Computer Information Systems Building</string>
    <string name="CISBuildingInfo">The Computer Information Systems (CIS) building was constructed to house
        the Information Systems and Operations Management Department from the Cameron School of Business and
        the Department of Computer Science from the College of Arts and Sciences. The CIS Building, a new 51,731
        square-foot state-of-the-art facility on the UNCW campus, opened January 10, 2007 for the new school semester. </string>
    <string name="CISCaption">Front of CIS Building</string>
    <string name="CIS_url">For more information, please visit "https://library.uncw.edu/web/collections/archives/bnl/cis.html"</string>

    <!--CAMERON HALL-->
    <string name="CameronHallName">Cameron Hall</string>
    <string name="CameronHallInfo">Funding for Cameron Hall began in 1985, with occupancy starting in 1988.
        As the home of the Cameron School of Business, the building contains classrooms and faculty offices.
        The official naming dedication was held on October 5, 1988.</string>
    <string name="CameronCaption">Aerial View of Cameron Hall</string>
    <string name="Cameron_url">For more information, please visit "https://library.uncw.edu/web/collections/archives/bnl/24.html"</string>

    <!--FRIDAY HALL-->
    <string name="FridayHallName">Friday Hall</string>
    <string name="FridayHallInfo">Opening in 1974 as the Marine Science Building, this structure became Friday Hall
        at its renaming dedication in 1986. The original purpose was classrooms and faculty office spaces for Department
        of Earth Sciences, the Science and Mathematics Education Center, Environmental Studies and Marine Sciences.
        The building now houses part of the Biological Sciences Department and offers additional space for graduate
        student offices. The Friday Annex is located behind this facility.</string>
    <string name="FridayCaption">Front of Friday Hall</string>
    <string name="Friday_url">For more information, please visit "https://library.uncw.edu/web/collections/archives/bnl/20.html"</string>

    <!--KRESGE GREENHOUSE-->
    <string name="KresgeName">Kresge Greenhouse</string>
    <string name="KresgeInfo">Opening in 1975, the Kresge Greenhouse is a classroom-laboratory which allows for a
        year round supply of salt marsh environment plants to be cultured for teaching and research. The funding
        for this facility came from a Kresge Foundation Challenge Initiative Grant.</string>
    <string name="KresgeCaption">Kresge Greenhouse on a beautiful morning</string>
    <string name="Kresge_url">For more information, please visit "https://library.uncw.edu/web/collections/archives/bnl/21.html"</string>

    <!--SHINN PLAZA-->
    <string name="ShinnName">Shinn Plaza</string>
    <string name="ShinnInfo">Dedicated in 2002, this plaza provides an area for students to hold informal meetings and discussions.
        The various materials used in the filigree dome, doric columns and pavement finishes contain philosophical symbolism
        in honor of Dr. Shinn. The University Seal is also located here.</string>
    <string name="ShinnCaption">Shinn Plaza within the woods</string>
    <string name="Shinn_url">For more information, please visit "https://library.uncw.edu/web/collections/archives/bnl/40a.html"</string>

    <!--RANDALL LIBRARY-->
    <string name="RandallName">Randall Library</string>
    <string name="RandallInfo">Funding to construct a library at the new campus location began in 1965 by the Friends of
        Wilmington College. The first on-site library was housed in Alderman Hall administration building following the move
        from Isaac Bear Building. In 1968, the original front of Randall Library faced College Road but since its 1980s expansion
        the entrance now faces Chancellors Walk. This facility contains UNCW Archives, Special Collections (Helen Hagan Room),
        the Gene Huguelet Conference Room, and the Honors Program offices, along with various faculty offices.</string>
    <string name="RandallCaption">Randall Library on a crisp fall morning</string>
    <string name="Randall_url">For more information, please visit "https://library.uncw.edu/web/collections/archives/bnl/3.html"</string>

    <!--WAGONER HALL-->
    <string name="WagName">Wagoner Hall</string>
    <string name="WagInfo">This structure opened to students in 1989 as the second campus dining hall (Westside was the first.)
        The Wagoner Dining Hall features food service with special events catering in the Madeline Suite. The General College
        was housed in Wagoner until its move to Westside following Westside\'s renovation.</string>
    <string name="WagCaption">The front of the beautiful Wagoner Hall</string>
    <string name="Wag_url">For more information, please visit "https://library.uncw.edu/web/collections/archives/bnl/39.html"</string>

    <!--DOBO HALL-->
    <string name="DoboName">Dobo Hall</string>
    <string name="DoboInfo">Opened for use in 1996, the New Science Building contained classrooms, laboratories and faculty
        offices for the Chemistry and Biology Departments. Known as Dobo Hall since its 1999 dedication to the Dobo brothers,
        it is currently used by the Department of Biology and Marine Biology and the Department of Chemistry.</string>
    <string name="DoboCaption">Facade of Dobo Hall</string>
    <string name="Dobo_url">For more information, please visit "https://library.uncw.edu/web/collections/archives/bnl/25.html"</string>

    <!--GALLOWAY RESIDENCE HALL-->
    <string name="GallowayName">Galloway Residence Hall</string>
    <string name="GallowayInfo">Originally called \'Dorm \'71,\' Galloway Hall was the first campus residence facility at
        UNC Wilmington. This building accommodates 400 students and was the first air conditioned dorm in the University of
        North Carolina system.</string>
    <string name="GallowayCaption">Galloway Student Living</string>
    <string name="Galloway_url">For more information, please visit "https://library.uncw.edu/web/collections/archives/bnl/29.html"</string>

    <!--LEUTZE HALL-->
    <string name="LeutzeName">Leutze Hall</string>
    <string name="LeutzeInfo">Originally called Lakeside Hall due to the building\'s location near the Commons lake,
        it became known as Leutze Hall in a 2003 dedication ceremony. Currently, the Departments of Communication Studies,
        Political Science, Foreign Languages and Literatures and Social Work are housed there. The film studies department was
        housed there until 2007 when it moved to King Hall. UNCW Media has a television studio in this building.</string>
    <string name="LeutzeCaption">Leutze Over the lake</string>
    <string name="Leutze_url">For more information, please visit "https://library.uncw.edu/web/collections/archives/bnl/17.html"</string>




    <!--IMAGE CONTENT DESCRIPTIONS-->
    <string name="buildingContentDescription">Building Descriptions</string>
    <string name="UNCW_logo_image">UNCW Logo</string>
    <string name="background_contentDescription">Wrightsville beach</string>


    <!--ACTION BUTTON-->
    <string name="action_info">About</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Action settings</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>


    <!--LOCATION-->
    <string name="request_permission_title">Where you at??!</string>
    <string name="text_location_permission">We need yo location bruh</string>
    <string name="grant_location_button">Hell yeah</string>

    <!--Navigation Drawer-->
    <string name="nav_about">About</string>
    <string name="nav_help">Help</string>
    <string name="nav_feedback">Give us feedback</string>
    <string name="nav_support">Support</string>
    <string name="nav_open_drawer">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_close_drawer">Close navigation drawer</string>


</resources>

